lonex.com 2012-10-19

# Lonex Privacy policy

**LONEX PRIVACY POLICY**

**PRIVACY OF YOUR PAYMENT DETAILS**   
We use encrypted SSL connection to process your credit card information and DO NOT store any of your payment details in our system. The payments are carried out in the background by the PayPal payment processing gateway and go through the HSBC bank's terminal. Working with the two leaders in online payment operations, we guarantee fast and secure processing of your payment. Not only do we NOT make a record of your credit card details in our system, but also - for maximum online security - we do NOT share this information with any third party. 

**PRIVACY OF YOUR ACCOUNT**   
We consider your registration data and the content of all your messages private and confidential. The header of the messages that you send will contain your name (e-mail address) and Internet Protocol (IP) address. We will not intentionally monitor or disclose any of your e-mail content or registration data unless we are required to do so: 

  * to enforce these Terms and Conditions, 

  * by law, 

  * to defend ourselves in any legal action, 

  * to protect our property. 

Since your password is essential for protecting your privacy, we encourage you to NOT share it with anyone and change it frequently. Additionally, you agree to respect the privacy and confidentiality of others. 

**PRIVACY OF YOUR REGISTRATION DATA**   
Lonex collects certain information during the registration process. The personally identifiable information that Lonex collects includes first and last name. Lonex also collects non-personally identifiable information, such as country, age, gender, etc. You may update your Registration Information at any time from your Web Hosting Control Panel - > My Account - > Change Login Credentials section. 

We may disclose aggregate registration statistics in connection with our marketing activities.

**WHY WE NEED THIS INFORMATION**   
Your registration information is needed in order for us to operate the site, to provide support for your account, for statistical purposes, etc. Lonex will NOT send you any unsolicited information, including e-mails, except as mentioned hereby.

**COOKIES**

We use different cookies on our website to make it as useful to you as possible. Cookies are small text files that we put on your computer or mobile device to tell us what you want to use on our site but they do not tell us who you are. 

[Here](http://www.aboutcookies.org/default.aspx) you can learn more about cookies and how to [control](http://www.aboutcookies.org/default.aspx?page=1) or [delete](http://www.aboutcookies.org/default.aspx?page=2) them. 

Here are the cookies that we use on our site: 

_Essential cookies_  
We use a cookie to remember your login for you and what you’ve put in the shopping cart. These we deem essential for the operation of our website. 

_Google Analytics_  
We use this service to understand how the site is being used in order to improve the user experience. The collected data is all anonymous.

_External web services_  
We use an external web service - YouTube, on our site to display videos within our web pages. We cannot prevent these sites from collecting information on your usage of this embedded content. 

Also, we use an external live chat service (using cookies to remember your session name) to deliver real time support to you should you want to.

_Payment processing_  
To process payments online, we require the billing address for the credit card used and our external payment provider, PayPal/WorldPay, requires your credit card details. 

We assume you are happy with this usage of cookies on this website. If you are not happy, then you should either not use this site, or delete the cookies (you can check out how to do that according to your browser [here](http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=2)), or browse the site using your browser’s anonymous usage setting (named “Incognito” in Chrome, “InPrivate” for Internet Explorer, "Private Browsing" in Firefox and Safari etc.).

Please remember that if you choose to delete the cookies or use the browser anonymously, you may find that certain sections of this website do not work properly. 

New customers will receive a Lonex welcome e-mail containing information about the features provided by the Service, as well as WHCP (Web Hosting Control Panel) and FTP login details. Lonex may also send system notifications upon need, related to any upgrade, maintenance or other service issues concerning your hosting account. 

Lonex will keep your personally identifiable information private and will NOT share it with any unauthorized third parties.
